Finding Aid for the Joseph Byrne Lockey Papers LSC.0127
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Central America
  - 43. Holland
    - Holland to Squier, April 8, 1859.; 4.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
    - Holland to Squier. 35 Albemarle Street, May 19, 1859.; 5.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75). (Box 3)
  - 44. Keeler
    - Keeler, David M. to Honorable George Squier. Geneva, Wisconsin, December 3, 1849.; 1.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75 paper).
    - Keeler, David M. to Honorable E. George Squier. Rochester, New York, August 12, 1850.; 2.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.5 × 11.75 paper).
    - Keller, David M. to [Unknown]. Utica, September 27, 1850.; 3.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75 paper).
    - Keller, David M. to [Unknown]. Rochester, New York, August 22, 1850.; 4.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.25 × 11.75 paper).
  - 45. Malmesbury
    - Malmesbury to Green, Foreign Office, June 18, 1852.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/29, no.4 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Malmesbury to Crampton, Foreign Office, August 9, 1852.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/543 no.76 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
  - 46. Marcy
    - M[arcy], W.L. to Shepard, L. R. Washington, April 15, 1855.; 1.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers - 8.25 × 11.75 paper). (Box 3)
    - Crampton to Russell. Washington, March 7, 1853.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5564 no.59 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Note. 1p. typewritten. State department., 3. (Box 3)
    - Marcy of Dallas, March 14, 1856.; 4.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department, April 7 1856). (Box 3)
    - Marcy to Dallas, April 7, 1856.; 5.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of State Department April 6, 1856). (Box 3)
    - Davis, Gilbert to Honorable William L. Marcy, New York, January 19, 1856.; 6.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers - 1.25 × 11.5 paper). (Box 3)
    - [Illegible] to Honorable William L. Marcy, New York, April 14, 1855.; 7.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers). (Box 3)
    - Lee, I.F. to William L. Marcy. 2pp. War Department, September 4, 1856.; 8.; (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers). (Box 3)
  - 47. Marcoleta
    - Marcoleta, de to [Unknown], May 21, 1856.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C.[?]). (Box 3)
    - de Marcoleta, T. to Honorable William L. Marcy. 2pp. Paris, February 16, 1857.; 2.; (Copy, photostat, of L.C.[?]). (Box 3)
  - 48. Napier
    - Napier to Clarendon, Washington, March 12, 1857.; 1.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/670 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Napier to Clarendon, Washington, May 6, 1857.; 2.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/671, no.66 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
  - 49. Norton, 1849
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Squier. Cambridge, April 3, 1849.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot. Boston, April 11, 1849.; 2.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, C.E. to Squier. Cambridge, February 7, 1867.; 3.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, C.E. to Squier, April 29, 1848.; 4.; 11pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to Squier. Cambridge, May 7, 1849.; 5.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
  - 50. Norton, 1851
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Squier. Cambridge, March 6, 1851.; 1.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Squier. Cambridge, April 19, 1851.; 2.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, C.E. to Squier. Newport, July 21, 1851.; 3.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Squier. Cambridge, November 2, 1851.; 4.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Squier, December 15, 1851.; 5.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
  - 51. Norton, 1852
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to the Honorable E.G. Squier. Shady Hill, January 19, 1852.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Honorable E. George Squier. Newport, August 14, 1852.; 2.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Honorable E. George Squier. Shady Hill, October 1, 1852.; 3.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Honorable E. George Squier. Boston, October 8, 1852.; 4.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Honorable E. George Squier. Cambridge, May 25, 1852.; 5.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Honorable E. George Squier. Boston, December 31, 1852.; 6.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to Honorable E. George Squier. Boston, January 7, 1853.; 7.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
  - 52. Norton, 1853-54
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to E. George Squier. Boston, January 14, 1853.; 1.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to E. George Squier, February 18, 1853.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to E. George Squier, February 1, 1853.; 3.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Boston, January 10, 1854.; 4.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Newport, July 11, 1854.; 5.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to E.G. Squier. Shady Hill, March 20, 1854.; 6.; 5pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Boston, June 30, 1854.; 7.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Newport, August 19, 1854.; 8.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Cambridge, March 21, 1854.; 9.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Boston, September 4, 1854.; 10.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Boston, October 18, 1854.; 11.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Boston, December 15, 1854.; 12.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Cambridge, May 7, 1855.; 13.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Newport, August 12, 1859.; 14.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Newport, August 18, 1859.; 15.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
  - 53. Norton, 1861-66
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Cambridge, April 12, 1861.; 1.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Cambridge, December 5, 1859.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to E.G. Squier. Ashfield, July 20, 1861.; 3.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot to E.G. Squier. Cambridge, January 6, 1865.; 4.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Cambridge, January 19, 1866.; 5.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. To E.G. Squier. Cambridge, January 26, 1866.; 6.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Cambridge, February 10, 1865.; 7.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier. Cambridge, February 27, 1866.; 8.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Norton, Charles E. to E.G. Squier, February 1.; 9.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
  - 54. Ouseley
    - Ousley to Clarendon, Washington, January 25, 1858.; 1.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/98 - Nor. 14 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Ousley to Clarendon. Washington, February 12, 1858.; 2.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/98 no.21. - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Ousley to Malmesbury. Washington, July 6, 1858.; 3.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/98 no.55 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
  - 55. Palmerston
    - H.U.A. to Home Office. Foreign Office, October 26, 1846.; 1.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 97/156 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Florez, F.O., October 2, 1846.; 2.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 97/156 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Florez, Foreign Office, January 14, 1847.; 3.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 97/156 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Flores to Palmerston. San Jose de Costa Rica Translation., October 13, 1848.; 4.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 21/1 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Wright to Palmerston. Trafalgar Square, December 5, 1848.; 5.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 21/1 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Cope. Foreign Office, December 16, 1847.; 6.; (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 97/156 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). 2pp. (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Crampton. Foreign Office, July 13, 1849.; 7.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/497, no.38 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Mr. Chatfield, January 17, 1850.; 8.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/63 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Green. Foreign Office, March 8, 1850.; 9.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/23 no.4 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Chatfield. Foreign Office, March 8, 1850.; 10.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 97/88, no.9 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Bulwer. Foreign Office, May 10, 1850.; 11.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/509 no.46 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Chatfield. Foreign Office, December 7, 1850.; 12.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/63 no.46 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Green to Palmerston. Grey Town, December 16, 1850.; 13.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/23b - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Bulwer. Foreign Office, January 21, 1851.; 14.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/525 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Green. Foreign Office, February 1, 1851.; 15.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/26 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Green. Foreign Office, February 1, 1851.; 16.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/26 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Bulwer. Foreign Office, April 4, 1851.; 17.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/525, no.50 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Bulwer. Foreign Office, February 20, 1851.; 18.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/525, no.20 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Bulwer to Palmerston. Washington, October 7, 1850.; 19.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/515, no.208 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Bulwer. Foreign Office, April 4, 1851.; 20.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/525, no.47 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Green to Palmerston. Grey Town, May 16, 1851.; 21.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 53/26 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Bulwer. Foreign Office, July 2, 1851.; 22.; 1p. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/526 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Palmerston to Crampton. Foreign Office, December 24, 1851.; 23.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/526 no.38 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
  - 56. Russell
    - Note entitled Mosquito., 1.; Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/561 (7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
    - Note, signed J.R., to Mr. Crampton., July 22, 1853; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 5/562 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 3)
  - 57. Sanford
    - Sanford to Squier. Geneva, October 10, 1856.; 1.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - [Sanford] to Squier. New York, December 6, 1856.; 2.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
  - 58. Savage (State Department)
    - Note. State Department., 1.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 3)
    - Savage to Marcy, October 31, 1853.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, typewritten). (Box 3)
    - Savage to Marcy, November 10, 1854.; 3.; 6pp. (Copy, typewritten). (Box 3)
  - 59. Squier, 1849-50
    - Squier, E. George to [Unknown], New York., February 21, 1849.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to Honorable John M. Clayton. Nicaragua, September 12, 1849.; 2.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to Honorable John M. Clayton. Nicaragua, December 12, 1849.; 3.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to Honorable John M. Clayton. Nicaragua, March 10, 1850.; 4.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to Honorable John M. Clayton. Nicaragua, April 9, 1850.; 5.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to John M. Clayton., 6.; 8pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 3)
    - Squier to Clayton, October 10, 1849.; 7.; 2pp. (including title page). Copy, typewritten, of State Department. (Box 3)
      - Declaration. S.D., October 10, 1849.; 1.; 1p. typewritten. (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to John M. Clayton., 8.; 8pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George., 9.; 1p. (Illegible.) (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 3)
  - 60. Squier--Bibliography
    - A List of Books, Pamphlet, and more important Contributions to Periodicals, etc. by Honorable E. George Squier, M.A., F.S.A., 1.; 8pp. (Copy, photostat, of Huntington Library). (Box 3)
  - 61. Squier, (Clippings)
    - Squier, E. George A Su Exceincia dl Ministro de relaciones extranjeras de la Republica de Costa Rica., 1.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George, to the Editor of the New York Herald. New York, September 23, 1850.; 2.; 1p. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Present Political Condition of Central America, and its Castes, March 25, 1854.; 3.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat.) article. (Box 3)
    - Alleged Treaty with Nicaragua. Article., 4.; 1p. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - America and Central American Affairs. Article for the Times, February 4, 1850.; 5.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - How Are Our Difficulties with England to be Settled? Article in the New York Herald, March 23, 1856.; 6.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in library of New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - American Affairs. The Albion, Liverpool, December 22, 1856.; 7.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in library of New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - The New Policy of Great Britain in Central America. Article in the Birmingham Journal, December 3, 1856.; 8.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, from original in the library of the New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - The New Policy of England in Central America. Article in the Morning Advertiser, London, October 23, 1856.; 9.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in the library of the New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - Mr. Squier and the Central American Question. Article in the Albion, Liverpool., 10.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in the library of the New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - Article in the Times, London, October 7, 1856.; 11.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in the library of the New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - The Honduras Settlement, article in the Daily Picayune, and The Final Settlement of the Central American Question, article in the Times, London, July 13, 1856 September 13, 1856.; 12.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in the library of the New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - The Common Sense Solution of the Central American Question. Article in the New York Herald, New York,, and duplicate in the Times, London, April 5, 1856 April 23, 1856.; 13.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in the library of the New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - Article on the Times, London, February 24, 1857.; 14.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of original in the library of the New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
    - Señor Don Jean Victor Herran, Honduras, Plenipotentiary. Article ( or place given.)., 15.; Copy, photostat, of original in the library of the New York Historical Society). (Box 3)
  - 62. Squier--Summary
    - Map of Central America, London., 1871.; 1.; 1p. (Huntington Library). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to Honorable W.C. Marcy. London, September 1, 1856.; 2.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers). (Box 3)
    - Command of the Isthmus. No name, 3.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers - 12 × 14 paper). (Box 3)
    - Manuscript(?)., 4.; 56pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 3)
  - 63. Squier to Norton
    - Squier, E. George to Norton. New York, December 24, 1852.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, March 16, 1857.; 2.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, April 15, 1851.; 3.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, July 9, 1851.; 4.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. Goerge to C.E. Norton. New York, July 13, 1851.; 5.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, August 8, 1851.; 6.; 2pp. (Copy, Photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, October 30, 1851.; 7.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, November 5, 1851.; 8.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat - 7 × 9 paper). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, January 3, 1853.; 9.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, January 10, 1853.; 10.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat - 7 × 9 paper). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, January 22, 1853.; 11.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat - 7.25 × 9 paper). (Box 3)
    - Statement (signatures not included)., 12.; 1p. (Copy, photostat.) (7.75 × 12 paper). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, February 11, 1853.; 13.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, February 15, 1853.; 14.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat - 5.5 × 8 paper.). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. Honduras, June 20, 1853.; 15.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. San Salvador, October 2, 1853.; 16.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. Lima, March 28, 1864.; 17.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, December 18, 1864.; 18.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, August 10, 1859.; 19.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat - 7 × 9 paper). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George to C.E. Norton. New York, March 23, 1861.; 20.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat - 7 × 9 paper). (Box 3)
    - Squier, E. George. Is Cotton King? A letter to Honorable H.B. Anthony, U.S. Senate printed in the Providence Journal, New York, January 25, 1861.; 21.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat - 5.5 × 9 paper). (Box 3)
  - 64. Walsh
    - Walsh, Robert M. to Honorable Daniel Webster. Greytown, May 28, 1852.; 1.; 5pp. (Copy, photostat, of S.D.[?] - 7 × 12.5 paper). (Box 4)
  - 65. Whelpley
    - Whelpley, James D. to Honorable Washington Hunt. New York, February 28, 1849.; 1.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 4)
    - Whelpley, James D. to E. George Squier. New York, January 24, 1851.; 2.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers - 8.5 × 11.75 paper). (Box 4)
  - 66. White
    - White, J.L. to [Unknown]. Staten Island(?), August 22, 1849.; 1.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers. (Box 4)
    - White, J.L. to Honorable John M. Clayton. New York, April 3, 1849.; 2.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 4)
    - White, J.L. to E.G. Squier. New York, April 4, 1849.; 3.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Squier Papers). (Box 4)
    - White, J.L. to Honorable William L. Marcy. New York, April 9, 1853.; 4.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers). (Box 4)
    - White, J.L. to William L. Marcy. New York, April 25, 1853.; 5.; 3pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Marcy Papers). (Box 4)
    - Clayton, John M. to J.L. White and others. Washington, February 12, 1850.; 6.; 2pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 4)
    - White, J.L. and others to Honorable John M. Clayton. New York, February 8, 1850.; 7.; 1p. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 4)
    - White, J.L. to Sir Henry Lytton Bulwer. New York, January 10, 1850.; 8.; 4pp. (Copy, photostat, of L.C. - Clayton Papers). (Box 4)
    - Bozland to Marcy, Extract of a letter from Joseph L. White Esq. to Lord Palmerston dated New York, January 11, 1854. November 12, 1851.; 9.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of S.D. -Dispatches from Nicaragua, vol.1 no.12). (Box 4)
    - Note., 10.; 1p. No name. Pencil, yellow paper. (Box 4)
    - White, J.L. to Honorable Jno. M. Clayton. New York, April 3, 1849.; 11.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Clayton Papers). (Box 4)
  - 67. Wyke
    - Wyke to Malmesbury, December 13, 1852.; 1.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/76, no.14 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - Wyke to Clarendon, November 27, 1853.; 2.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/79, no.37 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - Wyke to Clarendon, December 31, 1853.; 3.; 3pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/79, no.43 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - From Gaceta de Guatemala, Sent to Foreign Office with Wykes, 33: October 8, 1854. Translation, Occurences in Grey Town, general observation., October 6, 1854.; 4.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/82 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - Wyke to Clarandon. British Legation, Guatemala, July 29, 1855.; 5.; 7pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/85, no.38 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - Wyke to Clarendon. British Legation, Guatemala, November 30, 1856.; 6.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/ 90, no.70 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - Wyke to Clarendon, British Legation, Guatemala, April 26, 1857.; 7.; 5pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/95, no.32 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - Wyke to Hammond. British Legation, Guatemala, July 28, 1857.; 8.; 9pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/95 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - Wyke to Clarendon. British Legation, Guatemala, February 27, 1858.; 9.; 4pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/100, no.12 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)
    - Wyke to Hammond. British Legation, Guatemala, April 30, 1858.; 10.; 9pp. (Copy, typewritten, of Foreign Office 15/100 - 7 × 9 red margin paper). (Box 4)